let MCQS = [{
    question: "which language runs in a web browser?",
    choice1: "Java",
    choice2: "C",
    choice3: "HTML",
    choice4: "Javascrip",
    answer: 3
},
            {
            question: "Whichg of the following is used to create web pages?",
    choice1: "C",
    choice2: "HTML",
    choice3: "Java script",
    choice4: "Css",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "Opening tag of HTML is called?",
    choice1: "Ending tage",
    choice2: "Pair tags",
    choice3: "Closed tag",
    choice4: "Starting tag",
    answer: 3
},
            {
            question: "Who perfroms the most on-screen kills in the Lord of The Rings movies?",
    choice1: "Boromir",
    choice2: "Gimli",
    choice3: "Legolas",
    choice4: "Frodo",
    answer: 2
},
            {
            question: "How many Oscars did the 1994 movie Forrest Gump win?",
    choice1: "3 oscars",
    choice2: "9 oscars",
    choice3: "6 oscars",
    choice4: "12 oscars",
    answer: 2
},
            {
            question: "In which form did 'The Jungle Book' originally appear?In which form did 'The Jungle Book' originally appear?",
    choice1: "Radio Play",
    choice2: "Film",
    choice3: "Book",
    choice4: "An app",
    answer: 2
},
            {
               question: "Which city is the setting for the 1950s film musical Gigi?",
    choice1: "London",
    choice2: "Paris",
    choice3: "New York",
    choice4: "Rio de Janeiro",
    answer: 1
},{
               question: "What world-famous movie monster turned 50 in 2005?",
    choice1: "Frankenstein",
    choice2: "King Kong",
    choice3: "Mothra",
    choice4: "Godzilla",
    answer: 3
},
            {
               question: "what year was JavaScript launched?",
    choice1: "1996",
    choice2: "1995",
    choice3: "1994",
    choice4: "none of this above",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "Which of the following is not javascript data types?",
    choice1: "Undefined type",
    choice2: "Number type",
    choice3: "Null type",
    choice4: "All of the mentioned",
    answer: 3
}];